Guide to the Thomas Raynesford Lounsbury Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, Series I
  - Bartlett, John Pomeroy, 1892 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bartlett, Lemuel C., 1881 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bartlett, Margaret, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bartlett, Truman, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Barton, Charles C., 1885 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Barton, Mary, 1900, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Baskervill, William M., 1884 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bastian, August, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bates, Ernest S., 1914 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bates, Lindell T., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bates, Lindon Wallace, 1902-1906 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Batten, E., 1885 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Baylor, Frances Courtenay(*), 1882-1913 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Beach, Frank Cuyler, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Beach, William Nicholas, 1891 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Beales, LeVerne, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Beardsley, Arthur, 1873 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Beattie, Reginald, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Beecher, Willis J., 1883 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Beede, Frank Herbert, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Beers, Annie, 1903-1904 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Beers, Clifford Whittingham, 1905-1908 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Beers, Henry Augustin, 1872-1914 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Belden, Charles Pool, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Belden, Mary Megie, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Belding, John Eastman, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Bellamy, William, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Bemis, K. I., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Benedict, Dr. Arthur, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Benedict, S. N., 1885 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Bennet, Ludovic, 1885 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Bennet, Miss Harriet, 1896-1897 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Bennet, Malvina, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Benscoter, Warren E., 1906 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Benson, S., 1866 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Bent, Samuel A., 1882, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Berdan, John, 1899-1900 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Bergen, Henry, 1908, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Bergen, Mary (Mrs. Paul D.), 1910 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Bernon, Adolphe, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Berry, Jacob, 1871 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Besant, Walter, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Beyer, Dr. Franz, 1886-1887 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Biglow, John, 1905-1907 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bigelow, T. C., 1905 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bilderbeck, James C., 1903 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bill, Dr. Earl Gordon, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bingham, W. R., 1905 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Biographer
    See: George Barnett Smith, box 20, folder 422
  - Birdsall, Ralph, 1908-1909 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bishop, J. Adams, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bishop, Rev. Theodore, 1883 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bishop, William Henry, 1885, 1894-1896 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bispham, David Scull, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Blackmer, O. C., 1880-1910 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Blackwell, Robert E., 1894 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Blake, Francis Hayes, 1885 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Blake, Henry Taylor, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Blake, James Kingsley, [1898?] (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Blakeman, Noel, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Blauvelt, Augustus, 1873-1881 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Blayney, T. Lindsey, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bliss, Eugene F., 1904 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bliss, Frank E., 1904 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bliss, Frederick L., 1904 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bliss, John B., 1876, 1878 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bliss, Walter, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bobbs-Merrill Company
    See: Laurance Chambers, box 3 folder 75
  - Bocca, Silvio, 1898 (Box 1)
  - Bodley, John E. Courtenay, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bok, Edward, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bolter, Alfred, 1873, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bolton, H. Carrington, 1879, 1895, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bond, H. S., 1891 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Bond, Marshall, 1889-1895 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bonner, Mary Graham, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bosler, Mary, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Boss, Henry R., 1892 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Boughner, Leroy, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bourne, Edward Gaylord, 1896 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bower, John, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bowski, Adolf, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Boyd, Stirling, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Brackett, Anna C., 1892 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Brackett, J. Raymond, 1879, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bradford, Gamaliel, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Brady, Cyrus Townsend, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Brainerd, Erastus, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Brainerd, Mary, 1884 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Brainerd, Thomas, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Bramhall, W.M., 1892 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Branch, John A., 1906 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Brett, George P., 1894 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Brett, William, 1896 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Brevoort, J. Carson, 1881 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Brewer, Arthur, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Brewer, E. H., 1886 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Brewer, William H.(*), 1865-1902 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Brewster, James, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Brewster, Katharine, 1890-1891 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Bridge, Hedley, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Bridgeman, Donald S., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Bridgman, John, 1896-1897 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Bright, James W., 1896, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Bright, Marshall, 1883 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Brinton, Daniel, 1882 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Bristol, Eugene, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Bristol, Louis H., 1889, 1898 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Britton, John James, 1908-1909 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Brixey, Reginald, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Brockway, Zebulon, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Bromley, Isaac, 1896 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Brooks, Edmund, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Brooks, Morgan P., 1894 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Brougham, Henry, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Brown, Calvin, 1897 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Brown, Edmund F., 1898 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Brown, Edmund Woodward(*), 1872-1881 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Brown, Eliza L., 1895 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Brown, George L., 1896 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Brown, Horatio W., 1871-1912 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Brown, J. Macmillan(*), 1885-1905 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Brown, Mary Jane(*), 1872-1886, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Brown, Walter Lee, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Brown, William, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Browne, Francis, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Browne, George H., 1906-1907, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Browne, William Hand, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Brownell, William Crary, 1906-1913 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Brownlow, W. P., 1905 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Bruce, William R., 1892-1895 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Brush, George Jarvis(*), 1837-1911 (Box 3, Folder 56-57)
  - Brusie, Charles F., 1893 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Bryan, W. J. S., 1909 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Bryan, William Lowe, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Bryant, Elwyn R., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Buckley, Frank, 1912, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Bucklin, George, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Buehler, Huber Gray, 1897 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Buel, Clarence, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Buffham, George R., 1895 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Bulkeley, Morgan, 1893 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Bull, Henry, 1888 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Bullen, Arthur, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Bullene, Fred, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Bunnell, Otis Gridley(*), 1892-1909 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Bunner, Alice Learned, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Bunner, Henry, 1893-1895 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Burgess, Emma, 1902 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Burke, Charles B., 1890 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Burkitt, Robert, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Burlew, Noyes, 1879-1911 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Burlingame, Edward L., 1889-1904 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Brooks, Edmund D., 1914 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Burns, William Savage, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Burr, S. DeVere, 1882 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Burrough, Kenrick Deane, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Burroughs, John, 1904-1907 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Burrows, Lucien, 1876-1878 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Burt, Bates G., 1894 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Burt, Pitts Harrison, 1893-1899 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Burton, Bishop Lewis, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Burton, Richard, 1897 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Bush, Charlotte E., 1897 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Busk, Eleanor Joy, 1894-1913 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Buss, Kate, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Butler, Ellis Parker, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1890-1891 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Butler, Norman, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Butts, Nellie D., 1894 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Buxton, A. C., 1888 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Byrne, Henry D., 1914 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - C - General (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Cable, George Washington, 1900-1910 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Cabot, Henry B., 1902 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Cady, H. T., 1902, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Cain, J. L., 1878 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Caldwell, Edward, 1888 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Caldwell, John, 1890 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Calhoun, Henry Warner, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Calhoun, Martha, undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Callender, Guy Stevens, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    See: C. F. Clay, box 4, folder 86
  - Cambridge University Press
  - Cameron, Arnold, 1891-1906 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Cameron, Brewster, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Cameron, Henry Cary, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Camp, Alice Susan (Mrs. Walter), 1905 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Camp, Walter, 1895-1905 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Campbell, C. L., 1885 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Campbell, C. M., 1892 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Campbell, Emily, 1879-1890 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Campbell, Loomis J., 1887-1888 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Campbell, Mary D., 1903-1912 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Campbell, Mary T. (Mrs. Wellington), 1884, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Campbell, Matthew M., 1891 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Campbell, Wellington, Sr., 1874 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Campbell, Wellington, Jr., 1889 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Canavan, Michael J., 1904 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Canby, Henry S., 1911 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Canfield, Dorothy, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Canfield, James, 1897-1903 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Carey, William, 1891 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Carleton, E. J., 1878 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Carnegie, Andrew, 1908-1910 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Carpenter, George, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Carret, Madeleine, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Carruth, James Harrison, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Carryl, Charles E., 1896 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Carslensen, Emil, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Carter, Franklin, undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Casey, Thomas Lincoln, 1880 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Cassot, Arthur, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Caswell, Mary, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Catlin, Benjamin S., 1858 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Catlin, Hasket Derby, 1881-1912 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Caywood, D. G., 1872-1885 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Century Company(*), 1884-1887, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    See: Mary Avery, box 1, folder 16 See: Katherine Brewster, box 2, folder 46 See: Clarence Buel, box 3 folder 58 See: Richard Watson Gilder, box 7, folder 177 See: Robert Underwood Johnson, box 11, folder 248 See: Benjamin Eli Smith, box 20, folder 419 See: Katharine B. Wood, box 2, folder 517
  - Chalmers, Patrick, 1886 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Chamberlain, Charles, 1879 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Chamberlain, Joshua L., 1904 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Chambers, Laurance, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Champion, Wallace, 1906, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Chandler, Charles B., 1890 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Chandler, Robert, 1904 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Chapin, John B., 1882 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Chapman, Alfred, 1873 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Chapman, C. C., 1914 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Chapman, James D., 1910 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Chase, Frank Herbert, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Chase, George L., 1871-1872 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Chatfield, Charles, 1875 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Chawner, Mary Grove, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Cheyney, Mrs. Mary Bushnell, 1907 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Chesnut, F. A., 1894 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - City College of New York
    See: John Huston Finley, box 6, folder 146
  - Chew, Beverly(*), 1888-1906 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Chiarini, Cino, 1897-1898 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Child, Clarence, 1901, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Child, Mrs. Elizabeth, 1897 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Child, Francis James(*), 1871-1894, undated (Box 3, Folder 80-81)
  - Child, H. P., 1898 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Child, William, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Chittenden, Russell Henry(*), 1892-1912 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Chittenden, Simeon Baldwin, 1884 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Choate, Joseph H., 1902 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Churchill, Arthur H., 1915 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Churchill, G. G. C., 1878 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Clafin, William, 1874 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Clapp, John M., 1890 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Clark, Charles Hopkins, 1890-1913 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Clark, Charles P., 1891 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Clark, John E., 1902 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Clark, Lewis R., 1906 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Clark, Rose, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Clark, Walter, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Clarke, Charles Cameron, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Clarke, George H., 1882 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Clarke, Isaac Edwards(*), 1871-1896 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Clarke, William C., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Clay, C. F., 1911 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Cleaveland, Livingston W., 1906 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Clemens, Samuel Longhorne, 1900-1909 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Cluett, E. Harold, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Clymer, W. B. Shubrick, 1900 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Coan, Titus Munson, 1884 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Coates, William, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Coats, Mr. and Mrs., 1896 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Cobb, Mrs. Fanny, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Cobb, John M., 1893 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Cobb, Richard, 1893 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Cody, Sherwin, 1911-1912 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Coffey, George Henry, 1873-1874 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Coffin, Selden, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Coggeshall, George B., 1873-1906 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Coggeshall, Janet, 1886-1898 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Cohn, Adolphe, 1901 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Coit, Henry A., 1894 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Cole, Adella J. E., 1895 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Cole, Ashley T., 1908 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Colegrove, William, 1881 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Coleman, Henry F., undated (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Collier, Maurice Dwight, 1884 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Collier, Peter, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Collins, John Churton, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Colton, Arthur Willis, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Colver, A. W., 1895, 1902 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Comstock, Milton L., 1906 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Comstock, William J., 1894 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Conant, Ernest L., 1889 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Conant, Samuel S., 1880 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Congress of Religion
    See: C.A. Osborne, box 1, folder 342
  - Conklin, Roland, 1897 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Conkling, Alfred, 1889, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Conner, Henry F., 1894 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Conover, Charles H., 1909 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Constant, S. Victor, 1885 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Cook, Albert Stanburrough(*), 1889-1904 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Cook, George H., 1873 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Cooke, E. Jay, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Cooke, Mrs. Hedley V., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Cooley, R. C., 1905 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Cooper, Asahel Warner, 1898 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Cooper, Paul F., 1882 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Cooper, Philip Henry, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Cooper, Susan F., 1881-1882 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Cooper, Thornhill, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Cooper, Fenimore, Statue Association
    See: Ralph Birdsall, box 2, folder 37
  - Copland, Howard, 1906-1910 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Corbin, William L., 1899 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Corey, Ella J.(*), 1872-1900 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Corey, W. F., 1883 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Corning, Harvey H., 1873 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Corson, Hiram, 1877 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Cortissoz, Ellen Mackay (Hutchinson)(*), 1882-1895 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Corwin, Robert Nelson, 1892 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Coughlin, Jane, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Coveney, John A., 1905 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Cowin, John C., 1893-1894 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Cowin, William B., 1894 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Cox, Edward T., 187? (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Cox, G. C., 1905 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Cox, John, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Coyle, John, 1884 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Coyne, John L., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Craig, Neville B., 1906-1909 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Crane, Thomas F., 1872 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Crawford, F. Marion, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Creighton, William, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Critic
    See: Joseph B. Gilder, box 7, folder 176
  - Crocker, William Henry, 1884-1900 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Croffut, Bessie, 1911-1913 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Crosby, James Henry, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Croscup, George, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Cross, J. Ashton, 1902 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Cross, James Franklin, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Cross, Wilbur Lucius(*), 1894-1914 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Crow, Martha, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Crowell, Thomas Y. & Co., 1900 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Currier, Mrs. A. N., 1896 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Curtis, Charles B., 1905 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Curtis, George M., 1898 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Curtis, Mary Melbrook, 1890 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Curtis, T. W., 1887 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Curtiss, Maude S., 1890-1896 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Cushing, W. L., 1880 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - D - General (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Dade, Charles Townshend, 1893 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Daggett, David, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Daggett, Leonard M., 1897-1898 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Dahl, Annette Whitney, 1897 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Daly, M. A., 1911 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Damon, Theron, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Dana, C. A., 1859 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Daniel, Thomas H., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Dashiell, Mrs. Landon, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Davenport, W. S., 1908 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Davenport, William Bates, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Davenport, William Edwards, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Davey, Vernon, 1893 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Davies, John, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Davis, Albert, 1904-1905 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Davis, H. C., 1896 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Davis, Mrs. Lilian, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Davis, Richard Harding, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Davis, Robert, 1882 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Davison, Frank P., 1909 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Dawson, Henry B., 1887 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Dawson, N. E., 1905 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Day, Alfred Ely, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Day, George Parmly, 1910-1913 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Day, Wilbur F., 1896 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Dean, Aletta, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Dearness, John, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - De Forest, Erastus Lyman, 1875 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - De Forest, Henry S., undated (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - De Forest, John William, 1883 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - De Garis, Frederick, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - De Goll, Louis, 1888 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Degraw, Charles, 1878 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - De Heyman, Neville, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Denby, Charles, 1878 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Denio, Francis B., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Dennett, George William, undated (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Dennis, Dr. Frederick, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Densmore, James, 1880 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Dent, J. M. & Co., 1889 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Depew, Pierre, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Desmond, H. W., 1885 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Devereux, John Henry, 1882 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Dewey, Melvil, 1886-1914 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Dexter, Franklin Bowditch, 1872-1895 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Dey, C. W., 1887-1891 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Dial
    See: Francis Browne, box 2, folder 53
  - Dibble, Howard C., 1907 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Dibble, W. E., 1896 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Dickson, Frederick S.(*), 1902-1915 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Dihigo, Juan Miguel, 1909 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Dimmick, Richard C., 1875 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Dimock, George Edward, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Dixon, Richard F., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Dixon, Theodore P., 1905 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Dobbin, James, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Dobie, Armistead Mason(*), 1910-1911 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Dobson, Austin, 1892-1893 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Dodd, Cyrus M., 1892 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Dodd, Lee Wilson, 1900 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Dodge, Henry N., 1904 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Dodge, Louise P., 1902 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Dole, Nathan Haskell, 1900-1910 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Donaldson, Alfred L., 1912 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Dooley, A. H., 1884 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Doolittle, Mary B., 1902 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Doolittle, Theodore Sanford(*), 1866-1891 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Dorr, Eben P., 1879 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Dorrah, David Lewis, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Dorsheimer, William, 1884 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Douglas, Charles Henry, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Douglas, David, 1883 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Douglas, Robert Langton(*), 1898-1902 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Dowden, Edward, 1894-1901 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Drake, Alexander, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Draper, Andrew Sloan, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Drescher, Rudolf, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Driggs, A., 1887 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Drummond, A. M., 1907 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Dryden, John, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - DuBois, Augustus, 1879-1880 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - DuBois, Patterson, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Dudley, Charles Benjamin, 1873-1906 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Dunbar, Mildred M., 1912 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Duncan, John C., 1889 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Duncan, Schmucker, 1894-1899 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Duneka, F. A., 1909-1913 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Dunlap, Charles Graham, undated (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Dunn, Jacob P., 1912 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Dunning, Albert E., 1885 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Durant, Douglas, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Durbin, William W., 1895 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Dutton, Piers S., 1912 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Dutton, Samuel T., 1887 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Dwight, Harrison Griswold, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Dwight, Timothy(*), 1887-1898 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Dwight, Winthrop, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Dye, Charity, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Dyer, Cornelia(*), 1877-1900 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Dyer, Joseph, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Dyer, Katharine Joy, 1882-1884 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Dyer, Louis, 1899-1907 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Dyer, Mrs. Margaret, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - E - General (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - East, Sir Alfred, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Eastman, Elizabeth, 1893-1894 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Easton, Morton William(*), 1872-1895 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Eaton, Miss Alice M., 1892 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Eaton, Arthur Wentworth, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Eaton, Charles Edwin, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Eaton, Daniel C., 1875-1877, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Eaton, D. Cady(*), 1883-1910 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Eaton, George T., 1894 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Eddison, J. E., 1908 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Edgerton, John W., 1904-1905 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Edwards, Charles E., 1905 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Edwards, Edward Junius, 1898 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Edwards, William J., 1912 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Ehrgott, Sarah Bard Field, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Ehrich, Louis Rinaldo, 1894-1899 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Ehrich, Walter Louis, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Eldridge, G. Morgan, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Eldridge, R. C., 1908 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Eliot, Charles William, 1884-1893 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Elliott, Aaron Marshall, 1883-1891 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Elliott, Ellen Coit, 1904 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Ellis, Alexander John, 1878 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Ellis, F. S., 1893-1900 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Ellsworth, Duncan S., 1892 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Ellsworth, William, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Elmquist, A. Louis, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Elson, Louis Charles, 1894 (Box 6, Folder 136)